Welcome to the Rebecca Horn exhibition at Bank Austria Kunstforum Vienna.
欢迎参加奥地利Kunstforum Vienna银行的Rebecca Horn展览。
The exhibition was a very personal and actually a very special concern for me, Since I was lucky enough to meet Rebecca Horn as a young student in Berlin as early as the mid -1990s.
展览对我来说是一个非常个人的，实际上非常特别的问题，由于我很幸运能够在1990年代中期与柏林的年轻学生见面丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horn）。
when she had her professorship at the University of the Arts in Berlin.
当她在柏林艺术大学拥有教授时。
I rarely impressed me so much.
我很少给我留下深刻的印象。
Rebecca Horn has an incredible aura, at that time she was of course much younger, but she has kept her to this day.
丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horn）的光环令人难以置信，当时她当然年轻得多，但她一直保持着她的今天。
I am therefore all the more pleased that after many, many years I have finally managed to realize this exhibition and that the Bank Austria Kunstforum The director, Ingrid Brugger, also supported me very much and the sponsors made it possible.
因此，我更加高兴的是，经过多年的多年，我终于设法实现了这一展览，而银行奥地利Kunstforum导演英格丽·布鲁格（Ingrid Brugger）也非常支持我，赞助商使我成为可能。
We are now looking here in the room in which we work above all from the Tate Collection London.
现在，我们正在这里在这里查看我们从伦敦泰特（Tate Collection）的房间里工作的房间。
The Tate has the most comprehensive collection of your early work.
泰特（Tate）是您早期工作中最全面的收藏。
Rebecca Horn was born in Germany in 1944, grew up there, but then came to boarding school relatively quickly, at the age of ten.
丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horn）于1944年出生在德国，在那里长大，但随后十岁的时候就相对较快地来到寄宿学校。
She was by far the youngest daughter of four siblings.
到目前为止，她是四个兄弟姐妹中最小的女儿。
The family history is relatively moved and it lost its parents very early.
家族史相对感动，很早就失去了父母。
So she was in Hamburg in the 1960s, studied there and, above all, has relatively early, which was also the latest at the time, experimented with toxic fabrics, with polyester.
所以她在1960年代在汉堡，在那里进行了研究，最重要的是，当时也是最新的，这也是用聚酯蛋白酶的有毒织物进行实验。
Rebecca Horn has lung poisoning And got tuberculosis and was therefore in the hospital for a very long time and had to go through a long -term senatorial stay.
丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horn）有肺中毒并因此患有结核病，因此在医院里呆了很长时间，不得不长期住宿。
Here she started drawing and she was completely thrown at herself during this time because she was alone.
在这里，她开始绘画，这段时间在这段时间里完全被自己扔了自己，因为她一个人。
So, as she once described it, that was more or less in isolation.
因此，正如她曾经描述的那样，这或多或少是孤立的。
And so she could only deal with herself.
因此，她只能与自己打交道。
This meant that she then started to edit her body and space, which she could not really leave, so to speak, to be incorporated into her art.
这意味着她随后开始编辑自己的身体和空间，可以这么说，她无法真正离开自己的艺术。
She also never worked with polyester again, but the first work, In addition to these early drawings, you can read as storyboards for these films, for their early performance films, which we also show in the exhibition, all three.
她也再也没有与聚酯一起工作过，但是第一个工作，除了这些早期的绘画外，您还可以阅读这些电影的故事板，以及它们的早期表演电影，我们也在展览中展示了这三部电影。
And then she started working with very light materials, i.e. with fabrics, all kinds of textile, brands.
然后，她开始使用非常轻质的材料，即用织物，各种纺织品，品牌。
And also how you see here next to me This is the overflow, which is from 1970.
还有你在我旁边如何看到这是从1970年开始的溢出。
This is one of the first devices, where you can see your fascination, I think, for mechanical things, so also for that is a bit.
我认为这是最早的设备之一，您可以看到您的迷恋，因此也有点。
With these work just described, Rebecca Horn was already invited to the epoch in 1972 by Harald Seemann and then went to New York immediately after the documenta, where she has also lived the next 10 or 15 years.
有了这些刚刚描述的工作，丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horn）在1972年被哈拉德·埃克安（Harald Seemann）邀请到时代，然后在记录中立即去纽约她在接下来的10或15年中也生活了。
And of course the opportunity to get to know a completely different art scene and completely different influences.
当然，有机会了解完全不同的艺术界和完全不同的影响。
And on the side, on the side, on the side, on the side, on the side, on the side.
在侧面，侧面，侧面，侧面，侧面，侧面。
78, her first feature film is being built in New York.
78，她的第一部长片是在纽约建造的。
It is really remarkable that your handling or or the connection between your cinematic work and your installation and sculptural work is already evident here.
在这里，您的操控性或或与您的雕塑作品之间的处理或雕塑作品之间的连接确实显而易见，这确实很值得注意。
And that is also the focus of the exhibition that we show here.
这也是我们在这里展出的展览的重点。
So I am concerned with showing her the objects that we then see in the exhibitions usually came out of the film with her.
因此，我关心的是向她展示我们在展览中通常与她一起出来的对象。
It also depends on it, it has a great love for bastakites, i.e. that is, also for the silent film.
它也取决于它，它对bastakites充满了热爱，也就是说，也是对无声电影的热爱。
And of course objects, since the language was missing, play a much larger role in silent film.
当然，由于语言缺少，对象在无声电影中起着更大的作用。
I am here in front of the work &quot;Dialogue of the Silver Swing&quot;.
我在“银色秋千对话”的作品前。
This work is then to the What I just said The connection between your objects and the films is particularly characteristic, Since the swing or the motif of the swing appears both in her first film &quot;The Ein Dancer&quot;,
这项工作是我刚才说的您的物体和电影之间的联系特别是特征，由于挥杆或摇摆的主题都出现在她的第一部电影《 ein舞者》中
Above all, one of the protagonists rocks in the final sequence and then jumps out the window with the swing, so to speak.
最重要的是，一位主角在最后序列中岩石，然后用秋千跳出窗户，可以这么说。
In the second film, La Ferdinanda, sonata for a Medici villa, a separate room is dedicated to this swing motif.
在第二部电影《 La Ferdinanda》（La Ferdinanda），奏鸣曲为Medici Villa的奏鸣曲中，一个独立的房间专门用于此秋千图案。
It is also a central work there.
这也是那里的中心工作。
Of course, the swings have two meanings.
当然，秋千有两个含义。
Once it is of course something from childhood that made us all happy.
当然，从童年开始，让我们所有人都开心了。
And on the other hand, it has something calming, monotones and, as she shows, it can of course also be fatal.
另一方面，它具有镇定的单调，正如她所展示的，当然也可能是致命的。
Here too, the swings go against each other.
在这里，秋千相互对抗。
This means that when you are in the middle, you will be killed literarily.
这意味着，当您在中间时，您将被杀死。
I stand here next to Cutting School, which was created in the early 1990s and is a really extraordinary work in many ways.
我站在这里旁边的学校旁边，该学校是在1990年代初创建的，在许多方面都是非常非凡的作品。
Once because she works the only time on this scale with found materials.
有一次，因为她使用发现的材料在这个规模上工作的唯一时间。
These five doors are old doors that she chose.
这五扇门是她选择的旧门。
And I think it&#39;s really a very personal work.
我认为这确实是一项非常个人化的工作。
On the material again, Rebecca Horn was very close to Janis Konellis, the representative of the Arte Povera.
再次，丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horn）非常接近Arte Povera的代表Janis Konellis。
And you would actually classify that in this direction.
您实际上将朝这个方向进行分类。
Personally, it&#39;s called Cutting Through the Past, which means that through the story, cut through the past.
就个人而言，它被称为“贯穿过去”，这意味着通过整个故事，整个过去。
Can mean, she hurt you, you carry her around with you and of course, maybe it is, you also take revenge on her.
可以意味着，她伤害了您，您随身携带她，当然，也许是，您也要报仇。
I find formally It is a very poetic work that is also based on its principle that these doors have an uncanny beauty through their consciousness and allusions to past moments.
我正式发现这是一部非常诗意的作品，也基于其原则，即这些门通过他们对过去时刻的意识和寓意而具有令人难以置信的美丽。
So that&#39;s very poetic.
所以这是非常诗意的。
On the other hand, they are cut through a very sharp metal rod.
另一方面，它们被切成非常锋利的金属棒。
When I got to know him, I loved him so much that every time I thought of him I lost confusion in the street.
当我认识他时，我非常爱他，以至于每次我想到他时，我都会在街上失去困惑。
He was so strong.
他是如此坚强。
Behind me you can see the work Concerto dei Sospiri from 1997.
在我身后，您可以看到1997年的作品Dei Sospiri。
This work was originally designed for the Biennale, the Venezia, for a room, i.e. for a very, very large space in the main exhibition of the Biennale at that time.
这项工作最初是为双年展的委内兹设计的，用于房间，即在当时双年展的主要展览中非常大的空间。
Concerto de Suspiri is one of the big ones, Space -filling work and installations Rebecca Horns, for which she became very well known after their return from the states, Above all, she also dealt with history, i.e. with places that have written history.
协奏曲suspiri是其中之一，空间填充工作和装置丽贝卡角，她在从美国返回后就广为人知最重要的是，她还处理了历史，即写有历史的地方。
Once in Germany, in order to process certain German historical aspects, of course, And here, in this case, the work in Venice was created, for Venice and with material from Venice.
到达德国，为了处理某些德国历史方面，当然在这种情况下，在这种情况下，为威尼斯和威尼斯的材料创建了威尼斯的作品。
This is rubble and pallets from demolition -mature houses of the city.
这是瓦砾和拆除 - 城市成熟房屋的托盘。
In addition, Rebecca Horn has made a soundtrack in very different languages ​​of sighs, lamentations, lamentations, complaints.
此外，丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horn）的叹息，哀叹，哀叹，抱怨的语言非常不同。
Again, the poetry, melancholy, shows up.
再次，诗歌《忧郁》出现。
So it is always about the brutality of life on the one hand, but also about the beauty of life.
因此，这总是一方面是关于生活的残酷性，而且还与生活之美有关。
Behind me you see the peacock machine from 1981.
在我后面，您看到了1981年的孔雀机。
The peacock machine is again a work that plays a major role in a film, in her second feature film, La Ferdinanda, sonata for a Medici villa.
孔雀机再次是一部在电影中扮演重要角色的作品，在她的第二部长片《 La Ferdinanda》，《奏鸣曲》（Sonata）为Medici Villa。
Here, similar to the swings we talked about, the peacock machine also gets its own space.
在这里，类似于我们谈论的秋千，孔雀机也有自己的空间。
in which she moves.
她移动的。
The peacock also appeared in her first film.
孔雀也出现在她的第一部电影中。
So the feathers are such a topic that it often uses or the material uses them more often.
因此，羽毛是一个主题，通常会使用或材料更频繁地使用它们。
So there are other works where she works with springs.
因此，还有其他作品，她与弹簧一起工作。
This work is of course particularly beautiful because it is also moving.
这项工作当然特别漂亮，因为它也在移动。
These are white peacock springs, that&#39;s something very special.
这些是白色的孔雀弹簧，这很特别。
However, of course combined with text, as you can see behind me, and also with these rods in which there was mercury.
但是，当然可以与文字结合在一起，正如您在我身后看到的那样，还有这些汞的杆。
So here is really a relatively hard combination of mercury, which is a very dangerous material, and this very seductive peacock springs.
因此，这实际上是汞的相对硬组合，这是一种非常危险的材料，而且是非常诱人的孔雀弹簧。
And then she also dissolved the work from the film.
然后她还将作品从电影中解散了。
They are available in two variants.
它们有两个变体。
This is once the one we see here behind us.
这曾经是我们在这里看到的那个人。
And then there is the one that was shown at the documenta in Kassel in 1982.
然后是1982年在卡塞尔（Kassel）的Documenta上显示的。
You can only see the scaffolding practically.
您只能实际看到脚手架。
These are very fine rods that are very pointed and dangerous.
这些是非常尖锐和危险的非常细的杆。
And they make the same movement as you.
他们与您进行相同的动作。
The peacock machine here now behind me.
现在在我身后的孔雀机。
So one up and down and spread.
因此，一个上下传播。
And yes, that&#39;s the reduction, so to speak, where it will be very dangerous.
是的，可以这么说，这是非常危险的。
Here we see »Concert for anarchy«, one of the most famous work Rebekah Horns, actually an icon of her work.
在这里，我们看到了»无政府状态的音乐会，这是最著名的作品丽贝卡·霍恩斯（Rebekah Horns），实际上是她作品的偶像。
Of course, this is also extremely spectacular.
当然，这也非常壮观。
It is a concert wing that is hung on the ceiling.
这是一个悬挂在天花板上的音乐会机翼。
So here in the Kunstforum, real renovation and installation measures were necessary and all of this was realized together with a structural engineer.
因此，在Kunstforum中，必须采取实际的翻新和安装措施，所有这些都与结构工程师一起实现。
So as you can see, a very, very complex work.
如您所见，这是一项非常非常复杂的工作。
The special thing about the wing is, he plays an important role in her last feature film, Buster&#39;s Bedroom.
关于机翼的特殊之处在于，他在她的上一部长片《克斯特的卧室》中扮演着重要角色。
She describes it that way This is not just a wing But that is, so to speak, the piano, which freed itself from psychiatry and gave the pianist the opportunity to live, continue to live.
她这样描述了这不仅仅是翼但可以这么说，这是钢琴，它摆脱了精神病学，使钢琴家有机会生活，继续生活。
In addition, you can see a little work with sheet music, which is also a propary from the film, so to speak.
此外，您还可以看到乐谱的一些工作，可以这么说，这也是电影的推论。
However, the whole room around the wing is filled with the sheet music.
但是，机翼周围的整个房间都充满了乐谱。
I find the work extremely exciting, natural because it is once very sculptural, On the other hand, she works with clay and is of course because it hangs upside down on the ceiling, extremely spectacular and of course completely out of context.
我发现这项工作非常令人兴奋，很自然因为它曾经是非常雕塑的另一方面，她与粘土一起工作，当然是因为它倒在天花板上，非常壮观，当然也完全不在上下文中。
Blue Monday Strip was created on the occasion of her retrospective in 1993 at the Guggenheim Museum in New York.
蓝色星期一地带是在1993年在纽约古根海姆博物馆进行回顾之际创建的。
Rebecca Horne works here with a variety of typewriters.
丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebecca Horne）在这里与各种打字机一起工作。
This is a motive that she still uses in other work.
这是她仍然在其他工作中使用的动机。
On the one hand, she alludes to her literary activity Rebekah Horn does not only write scripts, But also a selection of it, but also poems and texts on your work, which we also show here in the exhibition on the work.
一方面，她暗示了自己的文学活动丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebekah Horn）不仅编写脚本，而且但也选择了您的作品的诗歌和文字，我们也会在有关作品的展览中展示。
And on the other hand, of course, this is a work where she comes back to an early topic, namely feminism or the role of women.
另一方面，当然，这是她回到早期话题的作品，即女权主义或女性的作用。
The typewriter stands for the secretary who has to write the letters that are dictated.
打字机代表秘书，他必须撰写所指示的信件。
The work, when it is in motion, through the rods that indicate the individual keys, this click-Klack results when typing on old-fashioned typewriters.
这项工作是在运动中，通过指示各个键的杆，当在老式打字机上输入时，会产生此click-klack。
And then ink is sprayed.
然后喷涂墨水。
Why Rebekah Horn now?
为什么现在丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebekah Horn）？
I find Rebekah Horn, apart from the fact that she is certainly the Grande Dame of German Art, she makes a very important point.
我发现丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebekah Horn）除了她当然是德国艺术的盛大贵妇之外，她提出了一个非常重要的观点。
So through the Corona epidemic we question everything.
因此，通过电晕流行病，我们质疑一切。
With her work, Rebekah Horn is precisely because you are the dualisms of our life, i.e. beauty, ugliness, brutality, love, hatred, Great emotions, also sensitivity with materials and with what is happening around us.
在她的工作中，丽贝卡·霍恩（Rebekah Horn）正是因为您是我们一生的二元论，即美丽，丑陋，残酷，爱，仇恨，激烈的情绪，对材料以及周围发生的事情的敏感性。
I think it fits particularly well into this time.
我认为这在这段时间非常适合。
And as Germano Celand says, She works on the disasters of life and gives us the opportunity to experience a new view of things through her objects.
正如德国塞兰（Germano Celand）所说的那样她从事生活的灾难，使我们有机会通过她的对象体验事物的新观点。
And I think this is a very, very important point.
我认为这是一个非常非常重要的一点。
I am particularly happy Because we succeeded Work like Concierto Dei Sospiri and High Moon, which really mean a huge effort and have been shown very little lately because of this.
我特别高兴因为我们成功了像Concierto dei Sospiri和High Moon这样的工作，这确实意味着巨大的努力，因此最近很少出现。
So that&#39;s really a premiere.
所以这确实是首映。
The last retrospective was seen in Austria almost 30 years ago.
大约30年前，在奥地利看到了最后一次回顾。
In this respect, I think it is a really great opportunity to rediscover this artist.
在这方面，我认为这是一个重新发现这位艺术家的绝佳机会。
So I really invite you to visit the exhibition.
因此，我真的邀请您参观展览。
It is until 23.
直到23岁。
To see in the Bankhaus of the Kunstforum Vienna in January and would like to point out the cinema in particular, That we have set up in front of the safe, where you have the opportunity to see all of your three feature films in full length.
在一月份在维也纳昆斯特福鲁姆的班豪斯（Bankhaus）看，特别想指出电影院，我们已经在保险箱前设立了，您有机会全长观看三部长片。